shiekh.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our websites. We recently updated our Privacy Policy, which outlines the information we collect, how it may be used and/or disclosed, as well as your options regarding these practices. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@shiekh.com.

Shiekh Shoes, LLC, its subsidiaries, or its affiliates (referred to as “Shiekh”, "we," "us," or "our" herein) desires to protect your information, as such we have developed this Privacy Policy, which describes the information we may collect when you use visit our located at, or linked to, the URLs www.shiekh.com, and the use of any of our co-branded websites that we maintain with one or more of our business partners (which website contains a link to this Privacy Policy) and the services that may be offered on each of the sites; our affiliate program(s) and corporate accounts; the ability to order products and receive newsletters and promotional emails; and any related links ( the "Sites") or mobile applications (the "Apps") (collectively the "Services").

Please be advised that this Privacy Policy replaces all previous policies regarding our data collection and information use practices. Please check back frequently as we reserve the right to change this policy, and to apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. If there are material changes to this policy or our information practices change in the future, we will notify you by posting the policy changes on this website. By using the Services, you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use the Services.

Types of Information We Collect & Use

We collect the information you provide to us while using our Services when you register on our Sites or Apps, place an order, participate in any of our promotions, surveys or product review, sign up for any of our loyalty programs and when you contact us.

The information collected from you may include your name, age, mailing address, telephone/cellular phone numbers, e-mail addresses, account user name and passwords, as well as payment information. If you use a third party login to register or otherwise link to us, we may receive certain information about you from the third party (such as a social network) based on your registration and privacy settings on that third party service.

Please be aware that you are solely responsible for updating the personal information you provide to us. If you have registered with us (see Account Registration below) or participate in any of our other loyalty programs, you may update your personal information through your registered account or loyalty program account. If you elect to delete some or all of your personal information, please keep in mind that we may retain transactional data in accordance with various laws, regulations and our company’s retention policy.

Account Registration

We encourage you to register when shopping on our Sites or Apps or when using our Services; however account registration is not required. Our registration process may require users to provide contact information (such as name, age, mailing address, telephone/cell phone number, e-mail address and password). Registration helps us to provide an expedited checkout process, as well as provide a more tailored customer experience. The customer contact information you provide will be used to contact you concerning the status of an order, answer your questions and, unless you choose to opt-out, to send you communications about upcoming sales, contests, promotions, newsletters and product information. You acknowledge and agree that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your registration information and password. You are responsible for all use of the Sites or Apps under your registered account. If you would like, you can also fill out a customer profile. While it is not required, information obtained from the customer profile questions helps us to learn more about our customers and is used to improve your shopping experience and to provide you with more relevant content and advertising.

We will never knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under 13 years of age without prior verifiable parental consent. **If you are under 13 years old, please do not provide your information on our website or attempt to register on our Sites, Apps or Services.**

Information We May Automatically Collect

We may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or other technologies to automatically collect certain information when you use our Sites or Apps, or interact with our emails or advertisements on our Sites, our Apps, or other Services. A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your phone or computer's hard drive. For example, we may automatically collect information such as your IP address, geographic location data, unique user ID, cell phone model, operating system, and carrier, and internet service provider. We also may collect information about your use of our Services, such as the time you spend using the Sites or Apps or Services, the number of times you visit, whether you click-through, open, or forward links, emails, and ads, and other Services usage data. These technologies, such as cookies, allow us to keep track of your order as you shop on our Sites or Apps, recognize registered users when they visit, and to provide those customers with information and advertising that is more relevant to them. If you register with or order from us, we may use cookies or other technologies to monitor and maintain information about how you use our Services and what you buy. If you do not register with or buy from us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use in order to improve your shopping experience and provide you with more relevant content and advertising.

California Privacy Rights 

Pursuant to California law, residents of this state are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or with corporate affiliates for their direct marketing purposes. We do not provide any personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. We however may share your personal information with affiliated third parties such as the Shiekh family of companies, some of which do not share the Shiekh name, for their direct marketing purposes (see below Use of Information Disclosure section for more information about these companies). This category of affiliate is considered an unaffiliated party under California law and, if you are a California resident, you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you want to request a notice or have any questions about our privacy practices or sharing of your personal information, please contact us at support@shiekh.com.

Tracking Options and California Do Not Track

You may adjust your browser settings to limit certain tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Services or take full advantage of our offerings. Even without a cookie, you can still take advantage of most of the features of our Sites or Apps, including making a purchase, but we will not be able to recognize you as a registered user unless you log in. Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers.

We may also use certain service providers to provide our customers with a more relevant online advertising based on their activities on our Sites, Apps and/or third party sites. To learn more about, or to opt out of use of this information by certain service providers, please click here [http://www.shiekh.com/account/unsubscribe]. We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with online advertising tailored to your interests. If you would like to opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, please click here [or email support@shiekh.com]. For certain service providers, such as social media platforms, and on your mobile device, you can adjust your privacy and advertising settings to limit your tracking for advertising or control whether you receive more relevant advertising.

Information We Collect From Other Sources 

We may obtain information about our customers from other sources, including social media networks that you use to connect with our Services. This information may include name, user name, demographic information, updated address or contact information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and online activity. We may also compile the information we receive from and about you from multiple sources, including the information you provide to us on the Services, through our promotional or loyalty programs, customer surveys, contest entries/submissions, information we receive from third parties, information we automatically collect (as explained above in Information We May Automatically Collect section), and information provided by you when you shop in our stores.

How We May Use the Information Collected

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Services, enhance the value of our products, expedite the shopping experience and communicate with affiliates and customers.  This may also include to notify you about special events, product launches, applications for employment or career opportunities, contest entries, membership or loyalty programs you apply for, in responding to your comments, questions or complaints, and other information you have chosen to receive regarding our products.

Use of Information Disclosure

We use the information we collect from you for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. We do not store your credit card information[[R1]](file:///C:/Users/theo/Downloads/Karmaloop%20Privacy%20Policy_NEW_rpw.081017.docx#_msocom_1) . If you have created a username and password to the site or if you have signed up to receive our email newsletter updates we may use your purchase history to personalize special offers and promotions for you. These offers and promotions will be delivered to you in the form of an email newsletter.  We may also share the information we collect from you and about you with Shiekh’s subsidiaries, including Shiekh Shoes, Shiekh, ShiekhToo, ChicShoes.com, TiltedSole.com, Eilatan.com, Sole, Broadway 7.15, FBRK Clothing.com, Karmaloop, PLNDR and Kazbah[[R2]](file:///C:/Users/theo/Downloads/Karmaloop%20Privacy%20Policy_NEW_rpw.081017.docx#_msocom_2) , as well as certain third-party partners. We also may use your personal information for our everyday business purposes such as service improvements, security, payment processing, analytics, operations, fraud detection and prevention, reporting, making back-ups and legal compliance.

**Please be aware that any personal or proprietary information or content that you voluntarily upload or submit for public posting to the Services (e.g., comments, pictures or other content) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. It is a violation of the Service's Terms of Use**[[R3]](file:///C:/Users/theo/Downloads/Karmaloop%20Privacy%20Policy_NEW_rpw.081017.docx#_msocom_3)  **for you to post content that requests personally identifiable information from other users of our Services.**

Please also be aware that it is possible that we may sell or buy other website or assets. In such transactions, information about customers often is among the transferred assets. Accordingly, in the unlikely event that our company or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, such information may be one of the transferred assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through the Services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. We may also occasionally share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about users of our Services with third parties.

Ability to Opt-Out

At any time, you have the option of opting out of receiving emails regarding special offers, newsletters or other marketing communications from us by [sending an email to [support@shiekh.com](mailto:support@shiekh.com) with the subject header “unsubscribe” or] by clicking on the link in the email you receive from us which will direct you on the process of opting out of future email marketing.  Please be advised that by using these opt out procedures, you may still receive non-marketing email messages from us to confirm your order, respond to your questions, etc.

Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.  Opting out will not stop these types of communications.

Supplementation of Information

In order to process your credit card orders, we use BrainTree/PayPal, a third party service, to validate and verify your account information. All billing and account info is transmitted via https which is a secure encrypted protocol system[[R4]](file:///C:/Users/theo/Downloads/Karmaloop%20Privacy%20Policy_NEW_rpw.081017.docx#_msocom_4) .

Legal Disclaimer

At all times, we reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website or company. You cannot opt out of disclosure of your personal information if required by lawful order.

Links to Other Sites

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by shiekh.com. Please be aware that we, shiekh.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.  As such, your access or use of any such linked websites or apps is solely at your own risk, and hereby waive any and all claims against Shiekh with respect to such linked websites or apps.

Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We use reasonable technological and physical safeguards to protect personal information you provide to us from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, however, we make all reasonable efforts to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information. In the unlikely event of a data breach, you will be notified as soon as possible.[[R5]](file:///C:/Users/theo/Downloads/Karmaloop%20Privacy%20Policy_NEW_rpw.081017.docx#_msocom_5) 

Customer Service

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the security on our Sites or Apps, or our data handling practice, you may contact us by email at [support@shiekh.com](mailto:support@shiekh.com) or by writing us at:

Shiekh Shoes, LLC

Attn: Legal Department

1777 S. Vintage Avenue

Ontario, CA 91761
